Finally, there might be things about Mike that make Mr. Ramos' words hurt more.
Some people feel things more strongly.
If they get a nice compliment, they feel really happy.
But if someone yells at them, they might get very angry.
We call these people sponges because they soak up everything around them.
Other people aren't changed or impacted as easily by things and people around them.
We call these people iron because they are hard to change.
Whether we are a sponge or iron has to do with our genes, how our bodies handle stress,
and how our brain works, things that start even before we are born.
But what's cool is that we can still change as we grow up.
So some people can start more like a sponge and move towards being iron or vice versa.
And all people are a sponge for some things and iron for other things.
That is, everyone has things that might bother them more than most,
as well as things that might bother them less than most.